(Sheldon:)All right, fine.
(Sheldon:)If we're not going
to give it a name,
(Sheldon:)can we at least give it
a secret code designation?
(Howard:)- No.
- Hear me out.
(Sheldon:)The atomic bomb
was The Manhattan Project.
(Sheldon:)Windows 95 was originally
Project Chicago.
(Sheldon:)For our app, I would humbly
suggest Project Nodlehs.
(Leonard:)That's just
"Sheldon" backwards.
(Sheldon:)Another happy accident.
(Leonard:)We're not wasting time
with names right now.
(Sheldon:)I see.
(Sheldon:)Is that decision open
for discussion?
(Howard:)No.
(Sheldon:)Is the decision to not
discuss it open for discussion?
(Howard:)No.
(Howard:)Again,
(Howard:)right now it's just
a dummy procedure,
(Howard:)but eventually,
it will drop us into...
(Sheldon:)I call for a vote
of no confidence
(Sheldon:)and an immediate change
in leadership.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, stop it.
(Sheldon:)When in the course of human
events, it becomes necessary
(Sheldon:)to dissolve the bonds
(Sheldon:)that tie three competent
scientists together...
(Leonard:)That's enough, Sheldon.
All right, let's get right to the vote.
(Sheldon:)Show of hands--
all those opposed
(Sheldon:)to Leonard
and his reign of tyranny.
(Leonard:)Okay, that's it, you're fired.